sheeparcade.com 2018-12-16

# Privacy policy

Sheeparcade Privacy Policy  
If you're reading this, it's because you want to know what information we, Sheeparcade, Inc., are collecting on www.sheeparcade.com or from Sheeparcade mobile games, what we're doing with it, and what your options are. If you have any questions or concerns after reading this, please email us at privacy@sheeparcade.com.  
This Privacy Policy applies to the Sheeparcade website located at www.sheeparcade.com (“Site”) and to all mobile games published by Sheeparcade (“Mobile Applications”). It also applies to information we collect about you offline, such as in telephone calls or through email correspondence.  
By accessing the Site and/or the Mobile Applications, you agree to and accept this Privacy Policy. This privacy policy is effective as of July 1, 2013. In the future, our Site or Mobile Application practices may change, and if appropriate, we will revise this Privacy Policy to reflect the changes, and you agree that the information we collect will be subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time we collect that information. We'll post the updated version here and may contact you with notices concerning our Privacy Policy. In addition, we suggest that you review this Privacy Policy periodically, as it may be updated from time to time.  
Information We Collect  
Information You Provide on Site: You provide certain personally identifiable information (such as your name and email address) to Sheeparcade when choosing to participate in various activities on the Site such as chat, posting messages in the games comment section or in our forums, sending feedback, entering contests, responding to surveys, or subscribing to newsletters or other mailing lists. Such information, and additional information (such as address and credit or debit card information) may be collected when uploading a game, or making a purchase.  
You may choose to disclose information about yourself in our online chat rooms, forums, game comments or in creating user "profiles". Information that you disclose in these areas is public information, and will be accessible to anyone who uses our Site. However, you may choose to have your profile page be public or private. In the case where you chose to make your profile page private, the information there (including challenges won, "my friends" list, etc.) will only be visible to you.  
Other Site Information We Track: This Site uses passive tracking technologies to log information such as IP address, browser type, pages visited, and Site usage (for example: what pages are accessed, how often, referring/exit pages and URLs). We may also employ "cookies" or similar technologies such as web beacons, match scripts, or pixel tags that provide additional functionality to the Site and help us analyze Site usage more accurately. You can set your browser to reject cookies, but if you do, some features on our Site will not function normally.  
Invite a Friend: You may invite friends to join the Sheeparcade community by using the "invite a friend" feature. You will be required to submit your name and email address, as well as their name and email address. Your friend's personal information that you submit in this feature will be used only to send the email you request, and will not be otherwise stored or maintained by Sheeparcade.  
Information You Provide via Mobile Applications: You may have the option to link your Mobile account to your Site account in certain Mobile Applications. This will allow you to participate in content that crosses between the Site and Mobile games, such as Sheeparcade level points and badges. If you choose this linking option the information we receive via the Site may also apply to Mobile Applications, and information we receive via your Mobile account may also apply to your usage of the Site and your Site account.  
Information We Receive Through Mobile Applications: If you play a Sheeparcade game on a mobile device (such as your phone or tablet) we can collect mobile device identifiers that can include things like your MAC address and IP address. We may also collect information such as device name and type, operating system, telephone number, country, and any other information you choose to provide such as your game character name or e-mail address. Additionally, we may access third party information such as your phone or Facebook contacts provided you allow your device to connect to services and you have given the application permission to access this information. We may only collect this information with your authorization and according to the rules you have established within your device permissions.  
Mobile Application Notifications: With your consent, Sheeparcade mobile applications may send push notifications to your mobile device to provide game information, news, updates, or other relevant information. You can manage these updates from the ‘options’ or ‘settings’ page from within the Mobile Application or from your device control panel that manages these notifications.  
Do Not Track: Do Not Track (DNT) is a privacy preference that users can set in their web browsers, allowing users to opt out of tracking by websites and online services. At the present time, the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) has not yet established universal standards for recognizable DNT signals, and, therefore, Sheeparcade does not recognize DNT.  
How We Use This Information  
We use the information we collect from the Site and Mobile Applications to respond to your requests and provide customer service, to remit revenue share payments, process credit card payments, let you know about new games and other news from Sheeparcade, ask for your input and feedback on what we are doing, provide personalized services and recommendations, to make certain offers available that we believe may be of interest to you, and as may otherwise be described in this Privacy Policy or at the time that we collect information from you.  
We use both your personally identifiable information and certain non-personally identifiable Site usage data to improve the quality and design of the Site and Mobile Applications, to make certain offers and available that we believe may be of interest to you,and to create new features, promotions, and services by storing, tracking, and analyzing user preferences and trends.  
We may also combine the information you submit to us with information we have collected from you in other forums, such as through emails or offline, or with publicly available information or information we obtain from third parties. When so combined, we or our business partners may use the combined information to make offers to you that we believe may be of interest to you.  
When We Might Disclose Information  
As part of our regular business conduct, we may share information with companies or individuals providing services or acting on our behalf, such as companies providing technological or fulfillment services or acting as our marketing partners. In the event that there is a change of corporate ownership, the new owners will of course be provided with our files, including information you have submitted. We will provide information in response to subpoenas, and we also will share information with government officials, including law enforcement officials or court authorities, in order to initiate or cooperate with any law enforcement or governmental investigation.  
Unless we tell you first (such as at the time we collect information from you), or unless it is part of a specific program or feature in which you have elected to participate, we do not share personally identifiable information that we have collected (such as name or email address) with other, third-party companies for their own commercial or marketing purposes.  
Links and Third Parties  
From time to time we may include at the Site or on Mobile Applications links to other websites as a service to you. The third party sites are operated by companies that are outside of our control, and your activities at those sites will be governed by the policies and practices of those third parties. We encourage you to review the privacy practices of these third parties before disclosing any personally identifiable information, as we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites.  
We sometimes work with third parties to add features, advertisements, or offers to our Site or Mobile Applications. These third parties may place cookies on your browser when you visit certain pages, or collect cookies that they have previously placed, along with the URL of the page you visited. We may have to pass these providers a non-personally identifiable user number specific to your Mobile Application to properly credit your account. Additionally, both the Site and Mobile Applications may utilize third party tracking services to anonymously analyze your usage activity, which will be used to improve your Site or Mobile Application experience. We do not control those third parties or their use of data. In some cases we may provide tools for you to limit data sent to third parties. This privacy policy does not cover those third parties’ use of data.  
To personalize the Site, and to simplify the registration process, we give you the option to link your account with Facebook. When you link your account, Facebook may share data about you with us, and we may share information about you with Facebook. In addition, Sheeparcade users who are your friends on Facebook will be shown your Sheeparcade username if you have both linked your Facebook accounts. For more detail on how this feature works, please see our FAQ.  
Security  
We use standard and reasonable technological and procedural measures to protect the information you provide. We urge you to protect your password by not sharing it with anyone else, and to take measures to prevent it from unauthorized access or disclosure. For example, select number and letter combinations that would be difficult for a third party (or hacking program) to determine, and do not write down your password next to your computer. To learn more about how to protect yourself online, we encourage you to visit the government's website at www.onguardonline.gov.  
Children’s Privacy  
The Site and Mobile Applications are designed for and directed at people 18 years of age or older. We do not knowingly collect information from children under 13. If Sheeparcade learns that a child under the age of 13 has submitted personally identifiable information online in contravention of these measures, it will terminate access to the account immediately and will take all reasonable measures to delete such information from its databases and to not use such information for any purpose (except where necessary to protect the safety of the child or other as required or allowed by law). If you become aware of any personal information we have collected from children under 13, please contact us at privacy@sheeparcade.com.  
For additional tips on how to help children stay safe on the Internet, we recommend that you visit the following sites:  
• www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens.html  
• www.ftc.gov/bcp/edu/pubs/consumer/tech/tec14.shtm  
• http://www.onguardonline.gov/features/feature-0002-featured-info-parents  
Your Options  
If you are receiving Sheeparcade email advertisements and no longer wish to receive those email messages, you may opt out at the time you receive the message by following the instructions in that email. Please allow ten (10) days for your request to be processed.  
If you wish to review and edit or delete information you have provided to Sheeparcade, you may access your account information on the Site at any time by clicking on your username at the top of the Site homepage.  
If you do not agree with the privacy practices described in this Privacy Policy, it may be best to limit your level of interaction with our Site or Mobile Applications, which could include simply not providing us with personal information. While this will limit the services that our Site and Mobile Applications are able to provide (chat, friends lists, challenges, etc.), most of the games will remain playable. This option may be best for those who do not wish to provide the mandatory information required to set up an account.  
For questions or concerns regarding the use of personal information you submit to us, please contact us at privacy@sheeparcade.com.
